<idea-plugin>
    <id>org.tera.plugins.Livy</id>
    <name>Livy</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
        The Livy Plugin enables executing code on a Livy server straight from IntelliJ and can show currently running Livy sessions
        with their properties.

        <h1>Execute code remotely on Livy</h1>

        <p>After installing the Livy plugin, select the code in your editor that you want to execute on Livy. Then right-click
        and choose 'Run New Livy Session'. This will start a new Livy session and immediately afterwards send your selected
        code for execution. The output from Livy will be shown in the output console as soon as the execution has finished.
        Unfortunately Livy does not support streaming Spark output as it would be supported by a Spark shell.

        When you want to change any of the Livy properties, right-click and choose 'Modify Run Configuration'.
        Alternatively, Livy run configurations can be created and edited in IntelliJ's Run Configuration Dialog.

        Once you have created a Livy Session, the plugin will automatically select that session for any new code you want to
        execute. If this is not what you want, you can open the run configuration and choose 'Create New Session';
        this way the plugin will create a new session next time.</p>

        <h1>View and Manage Livy sessions</h1>

        <p>To view all Livy's running sessions, go to 'View'/'Tool Windows' and choose 'Livy Sessions'.Livy sessions will be shown
        when 'Refresh' is clicked. After selecting a session it is possible to delete it, but make sure that that session is
        yours! The sessions that are shown are the ones that are running on the Livy server that you configured in your most
        recent Livy run configuration.</p>

        <h1>Editing settings</h1>

        <p>For a new run configuration, the Livy plugin will copy the settings from your last configuration, such as the host to
        connect to and all Spark configuration. You can edit the run configuration to adjust any settings.There is also a
        Livy Settings menu under Preferences-Tools-Livy Settings that lets you edit a few defaults such as the auto-generated
        prefix for the session name.</p>
        ]]>
    </description>
    <version>0.3.2</version>
    <change-notes>Initial release of the plugin.</change-notes>
    <vendor>Misja Alma</vendor>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <configurationType implementation="org.tera.plugins.livy.run.LivyConfigurationType"/>
        <runConfigurationProducer implementation="org.tera.plugins.livy.run.LivyRunConfigurationProducer"/>
        <toolWindow id="Livy Sessions" secondary="true" icon="AllIcons.Actions.ArrowExpand" anchor="bottom"
                    factoryClass="org.tera.plugins.livy.sessions.SessionsPanelFactory"/>
        <applicationConfigurable parentId="tools" instance="org.tera.plugins.livy.settings.LivyAppSettingsConfigurable"
                             id="org.tera.plugin.Livy.LivyAppSettingsConfigurable" displayName="Livy Settings"/>
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="org.tera.plugins.livy.settings.AppSettingsState"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
