<idea-plugin>
    <id>org.tera.plugins.Livy</id>
    <name>Livy</name>
    <description><![CDATA[
        Enables executing code on an Apache Livy server directly from IntelliJ.
        <a href="https://livy.apache.org/">Apache Livy</a> is a REST service that enables remote execution of Spark jobs.

        Features of the Livy Plugin:
        <ul>
            <li>Select code in your editor and execute it on your Livy server, either in a new session or by reusing an existing one</li>
            <li>Displays the output of your Livy job in the terminal window</li>
            <li>Show and manage currently running Livy sessions</li>
        </ul>

        <h1>Usage Instructions</h1>

        <p>After installing the Livy plugin, it's a good idea to enter the default settings of your Livy server.
        Under preferences -> Livy Settings you can enter the host address, default Livy configuration json and a default
        session name prefix.</p>

        <h1>Running code on a Livy server</h1>

        <img src="dropdown.png"/>

        <p>Select the code in your editor that you want to execute. Then right-click and choose 'Run New Livy Session'.
        This will start a new Livy session using the default Livy settings and immediately send your selected
        code for execution. The output from Livy will be shown in the output console.
        Unfortunately Livy does not support streaming Spark output as it would be supported by a Spark shell, so any
        output of your job will be shown at then end, when your job has completed.

        When you want to change any of the Livy properties, right-click and choose 'Modify Run Configuration'.
        Alternatively, Livy run configurations can be created and edited in IntelliJ's Run Configuration Dialog.

        Once you have created a Livy Session, the plugin will automatically show that last session in the context menu for
        any new code you want to execute, so you can choose to execute new code in the same session.</p>

        <h1>View and Manage Livy sessions</h1>

        <img src="sessions.png"/>

        <p>To view all Livy's running sessions, go to 'View'/'Tool Windows' and choose 'Livy Sessions'.Livy sessions will be shown
        when 'Refresh' is clicked. After selecting a session it is possible to delete it, but make sure that that session is
        yours! The sessions that are shown are the ones that are running on the Livy server that you configured in your most
        recent Livy run configuration.</p>

        <h1>Editing settings</h1>

        <p>For a new run configuration, the Livy plugin will copy the settings from your last configuration, such as the host to
        connect to and all Spark configuration. You can edit the run configuration to adjust any settings.There is also a
        Livy Settings menu under Preferences-Tools-Livy Settings that lets you edit a few defaults such as the auto-generated
        prefix for the session name.</p>
        ]]>
    </description>
    <version>0.0.51</version>
    <change-notes>Initial release of the plugin.</change-notes>
    <vendor>Misja Alma</vendor>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <configurationType implementation="org.tera.plugins.livy.run.LivyConfigurationType"/>
        <runConfigurationProducer implementation="org.tera.plugins.livy.run.LivyRunConfigurationProducer"/>
        <toolWindow id="Livy Sessions" secondary="true" icon="AllIcons.Actions.ArrowExpand" anchor="bottom"
                    factoryClass="org.tera.plugins.livy.sessions.SessionsPanelFactory"/>
        <applicationConfigurable parentId="tools" instance="org.tera.plugins.livy.settings.LivyAppSettingsConfigurable"
                             id="org.tera.plugin.Livy.LivyAppSettingsConfigurable" displayName="Livy Settings"/>
        <applicationService serviceImplementation="org.tera.plugins.livy.settings.AppSettingsState"/>
    </extensions>

    <actions>
        <!-- See AllIcons.class for more icons -->
        <action id="org.tera.plugins.livy.run.new" class="org.tera.plugins.livy.run.NewLivySession" text="Run New Livy Session"
                description="Run New Livy Session" icon="/runConfigurations/testState/run.svg">
            <add-to-group group-id="EditorPopupMenu.Run" anchor="first"/>
        </action>
    </actions>

</idea-plugin>
